[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother
George.
[GRUNTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
[SNORTS]
And this is Daddy Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[TV CHARACTERS GIBBERING]
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
[GRUNTS]
[GIBBERING]
[LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLING]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig wears glasses.
He needs to wear glasses,
to see clearly.
When Daddy Pig wears his
glasses, everything looks fine.
[GIBBERING]
NARRATOR: But when Daddy Pig
takes his glasses off...
he can't see things clearly.
Everything looks
a bit soft and fuzzy.
So, it is very important
that Daddy Pig knows
where his glasses are.
[GIBBERING]
[GRUNTS]
Hm.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: Sometimes Daddy Pig
loses his glasses.
Peppa. George.
Have you seen
Daddy Pig's glasses?
He can't find them
anywhere.
[GRUNTS]
No, Mommy.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George do not know
where Daddy Pig's glasses are.
[SNORTS]
Oh, dear.
Daddy Pig cannot see
a thing without them.
And it makes him
very grumpy.
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
Without his glasses on,
Daddy Pig cannot read
his newspaper.
[SNORT]
This is ridiculous!
I can't see anything!
Somebody must have put
my glasses somewhere.
[SNORTS]
Do you remember where you
last put them, Daddy Pig?
When I don't wear them,
I always put them in my pocket.
[SNORTS]
But they aren't there now.
Daddy! Can we help
find your glasses?
MOMMY PIG:
Good idea, Peppa.
If you find them, Daddy will
stop being so grumpy.
I'm not grumpy.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are looking
for Daddy's glasses.
NARRATOR:
Peppa looks under
the newspaper.
But Daddy Pig's glasses
are not there.
Oh.
NARRATOR:
George looks on top
of the television.
But Daddy Pig's glasses
are not there.
Oh.
[SNORTS]
Let's look upstairs,
in Mommy and Daddy's bedroom!
[GRUNTING, GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are looking in
Mommy and Daddy Pig's bedroom.
George, be careful not
to knock anything over.
Ah!
[SNORTS, LAUGHS]
It's not funny.
NARRATOR:
Peppa looks under the pillows.
But Daddy Pig's glasses
are not there.
Oh.
NARRATOR: George looks
in Daddy's slippers.
But the glasses
are not there either.
[SNIFFS, COUGHS]
[GIGGLES, GRUNTS]
Let's look in the bathroom!
[BOTH LAUGH]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
are looking in the bathroom.
The glasses
are not in the bath.
Oh.
The glasses are not
in the toilet.
[ECHOES]
Oh.
Hm.
[SNORTS]
It's too difficult.
[GRUNTS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George cannot find
Daddy Pig's glasses anywhere.
[SNORTS]
We've looked everywhere.
But we can't find
Daddy's glasses.
Oh, dear.
Now what can we do?
I suppose I'll just have
to learn to do without them.
[SNORTS]
If I move slowly
I won't bump into things.
[GRUNTS]
There they are!
Daddy's glasses!
[SNORTS]
Daddy Pig.
You were sitting
on them all the time!
Oh...
[LAUGHS]
Silly Daddy!
[LAUGHS, GRUNTS]
I don't know how they got there.
[LAUGHS]
I wonder how!
[GRUNTING, LAUGHING]
He-he-he-he-he!
[GRUNTS]
Well, you may have been
a bit silly, Daddy Pig,
but at least you're
not grumpy anymore!
I was not grumpy.
[LAUGHING, GRUNTING]
[ALL GUFFAWING]
[♪♪♪]
[HORN HONKS]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are playing
at Granny Pig
and Grandpa Pig's house.
[GIGGLING]
Grandpa! Catch!
Ho-ho-ho!
[SNORTS]
Catch!
[LAUGHS]
He-he-he.
[SNORTS]
What's this?
Dine-saw! Grrrrr!
A dinosaur!
[LAUGHING]
Grandpa,
what are you doing?
I'm planting these seeds.
Seeds?
What do seeds do?
Seeds grow into plants.
I just make a little hole
and put the seed in.
Then I cover it with earth
and water it.
[SNORTS]
Everything in my garden
grows from tiny seeds
like these.
Even the big apple tree?
Oh! Yes!
[SNORTS]
This tiny seed
will grow into a little
apple tree like this.
Snort!
BOTH: Ooh.
And that
little apple tree
will grow into
a big apple tree like this.
Ouch!
[SNORTS]
Mm.
[CRUNCHES]
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[LAUGHS, SNORTS]
And inside this apple
are more seeds.
[SNORTS]
To make more apple trees!
Exactly!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
[SNORTS]
I want to plant a seed!
Would you like to plant
a strawberry seed?
Yes, please!
This seed will grow into
a lovely strawberry plant.
First,
make a little hole.
Then I put the seed in...
and cover it with earth.
Shall I water it for you?
No! No!
[SNORTS]
I want to water it.
Good!
[GRUNTS]
Now we wait for it
to grow.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are waiting
for the seed to grow.
[GRUNTS]
It's not doing anything!
No-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho.
You'll have to be
patient, Peppa.
[SNORTS]
It will take
a long time to grow.
Peppa! George!
It's time to go home.
But we're waiting for my
strawberry plant to grow!
[SNORTS]
I wanted
strawberries for tea.
GRANDPA PIG:
Don't worry, Peppa.
[SNORTS]
Next time you come,
the seed will have grown
into a plant.
[SNORTS]
And we'll have strawberries!
Yes!
[SNORT]
Come on, Peppa.
Bye bye, Grandpa.
Bye bye, strawberry.
[KISSES, GIGGLES]
[SNORTING, GIGGLING]
[STARTS ENGINE, HONKS]
NARRATOR: Grandpa Pig looks
after Peppa's strawberry plant.
After many days, Grandpa Pig
finds a tiny plant growing.
Day by day, the plant grows
bigger and bigger.
Then one day, Grandpa Pig finds
something very special.
GRANDPA PIG:
Strawberries!
[SNORTS]
Grandpa! We're back!
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
have come to play again.
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Did my plant grow?
Yes! Look!
BOTH: Ooh!
Strawberries!
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]
Thank you, Grandpa!
[NIBBLING]
Grandpa, can we plant
something else?
Yes!
[SNORTS]
Now it's George's turn
to choose.
[GRUNTS]
Yes! You choose, George.
Choose a carrot!
[SNORTS]
Grandpa,
I think George wants
to grow a carrot.
George, would you
like to grow a carrot?
[GRUNTS]
No!
What would you like to grow?
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR: George has thought
of something he wants to grow.
[SNORTS]
Dine-saw!
NARRATOR: George wants
to grow a dinosaur tree!
[GIGGLES]
Silly George!
[SNORTS]
Dinosaurs don't
grow on trees.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Dine-saw! Grrr!
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[CRUNCHING]
NARRATOR: Peppa, George, Mommy
and Daddy are having breakfast.
It is a lovely,
sunny day,
and Peppa and George
can't wait
to go into the garden
to play.
[SNORTS]
Mommy, please can
we go out to play?
[SNORTS]
You can go out to play
when you finish your breakfast.
[MUNCHING, SLURPING]
[CRUNCHES, SLURPS]
George!
[SNORTS]
Don't drink your juice
too quickly!
[HICCUPS]
[GIGGLES]
He-he-he!
NARRATOR: George drank
his juice too quickly,
and now he has hiccups.
[HICCUPS]
[ALL LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
Can we go out
to play now, Mommy?
Not while
George has hiccups.
But George's hiccups
have gone, Mommy.
Haven't they, George?
[HICCUPS]
[ALL LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
Oh, all right, you can
go out and play.
But look after George.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George love
playing in the garden.
George. I'm going
to throw the ball,
and then you
have to catch it.
[HICCUPS]
George.
Please stop hiccuping!
[HICCUPS]
George!
Now you throw the ball to me
and I have to catch it.
[HICCUPS]
George!
NARRATOR: Oh dear, George's
hiccups are spoiling the game.
George, I know
how to cure hiccups!
You have to do what I say.
[HICCUPS]
[GIGGLES]
[SNORTS]
Rub the top of your head
and rub your tummy.
Good! Now your hiccups
have gone!
[HICCUPS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa's cure for hiccups
doesn't seem to have worked.
George! You have done it
all wrong!
I know better way
to cure hiccups!
First, jump up and down
three times on one leg!
Now, wave your arms
up and down,
and stick your tongue out!
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[BLOWS RASPBERRIES]
And now,
close your eyes,
and turn around quickly,
three times!
[HICCUPS]
NARRATOR: Peppa's new cure
hasn't worked either,
George still has hiccups.
[HICCUPS]
I know!
To cure hiccups, the ill piggy
must be given a shock!
George,
I'm going to scare you.
But you must remember,
it's only a game and it will
stop your hiccups.
Remember, this is
just pretend scaring.
[GRUNTS LOUDLY]
[CRYING]
MOMMY PIG:
Peppa!
You mustn't play
so roughly with George!
He's only little.
Sorry, Mommy.
I was trying to stop
George's hiccups.
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
George's hiccups have gone!
Here comes Daddy Pig,
with two beakers of juice.
[SNORTS]
George!
If you drink too quickly,
you will get hiccups again!
I'm not as little
as George,
I can drink juice
as quickly as I want to!
[SLURPS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[HICCUPS]
[LAUGHS]
[ALL LAUGH, SNORT]
[HICCUPS, GIGGLES]
[ALL GUFFAWING]
[HICCUPS]
[HICCUPS, GIGGLES]
[♪♪♪]
[BICYCLE BELL RINGS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
It is a lovely sunny day,
and Peppa and George
are riding their bicycles.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
[BICYCLE BELL RINGS]
[SNORTS]
That's a fine pumpkin,
Daddy Pig!
NARRATOR: Daddy Pig is
very proud of his pumpkin.
Pumpkins are the only
thing I can grow.
Probably because
I love pumpkin pie!
[SNORTS]
[BICYCLE BELL RINGS]
Come on, George.
[PANTING]
Danny, Suzy, Rebecca!
NARRATOR: Peppa and her friends
Danny Dog, Suzy Sheep,
and Rebecca Rabbit are riding
their bicycles.
George is riding
his tricycle.
He's going so slowly.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[PANTING, SNORTS]
Woof! Let's race
to Daddy Pig's pumpkin.
PEPPA:
If we race to
Daddy's pumpkin,
we have be very careful
not to bump into it.
[SNORTS]
Daddy would be very sad
if the pumpkin got broken.
Don't worry, Peppa.
Race you! Woof! Woof!
[LAUGHING]
[BICYCLE BELLS RINGING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her friends are
racing to Daddy Pig's pumpkin!
Hey! Watch out
for my pumpkin!
Hooray! Woof! Woof!
[LAUGHING]
[BELLS RING]
MOMMY PIG:
Peppa! Look out!
Daddy's pumpkin!
Ah!
Sorry, Daddy!
[SNORTS]
[BICYCLE BELL RINGS]
PEPPA:
Look at George!
He's going so slowly!
[CHUCKLES, GRUNTS]
George is still riding
a baby bike!
Woof! Yours is a baby bike
too, Peppa!
You've still got
stabilizers!
I can ride
without my stabilizers.
Baaa! Me too.
And me. Woof! Woof!
[♪♪♪]
Let's ride up
the hill again! Woof!
Are you coming, Peppa?
No, I think I'll stay here.
Woof! Woof!
Baaa! See you later!
Bye.
NARRATOR:
Peppa wishes she did not have
stabilizers on her bicycle.
[SNORTS]
Daddy, I don't want
stabilizers anymore.
Do you think you can ride
without them?
[SNORTS]
Yes.
All right, Peppa.
Let's take them off.
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig is taking
the stabilizers
off Peppa's bicycle.
Are you sure you want to ride
without stabilizers?
Yes!
You've never done it before.
[SNORTS]
I can do it. I can, I can.
Aah!
[GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]
It's not funny!
NARRATOR: Riding without
stabilizers is not easy.
[SNORTS]
Would you like some help, Peppa?
Yes, please, Daddy.
All right.
[SNORTS]
Ready. Steady. Go!
Don't let go, Daddy!
Don't worry.
I've got you.
You're doing
really well, Peppa.
[GRUNTS]
Hold on, Daddy!
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Just keep pedaling.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is riding on her own,
without stabilizers!
[BRAKES SCREECH]
Daddy! You let go!
Ha, ha. You've been cycling
on your own for ages.
Have I?
You're really
very good at it!
Am I?
Oh I can do it!
Look at me! Look at me!
I can ride my bike properly.
[SNORTS]
[RINGS BELL]
Danny! Suzy! Rebecca! Look!
I don't need
my stabilizers anymore!
[SNORTS]
Look at me!
ALL: Hooray!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Race you
to Daddy's pumpkin!
[LAUGHING]
[BELLS RING]
Wheeeee!
[RINGS BELL]
Peppa, look out, my pumpkin!
[GRUNTS]
I'm going to win!
NARRATOR: Peppa isn't looking
where she is going!
[BRAKES SCREECH]
Wahhhh!
[SPLOSH]
Whoops!
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear.
Peppa has squashed
Daddy Pig's pumpkin!
Sorry I squashed
your pumpkin, Daddy.
[SNORTS]
Never mind the pumpkin.
The important thing
is that you are okay.
In future, you really must
look where you are going.
I promise I will, Daddy.
Good.
Anyway, now the pumpkin
is broken,
I can make it into
pumpkin pie!
I love pumpkin pie!
[GRUNTS]
And because Daddy Pig's
pumpkin is so big,
there will be enough
pumpkin pie for everyone!
KIDS: Hooray!
[ALL LAUGH]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING, SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING, GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]